ELISABETH SEMEL PAPERS (APAP332) 1977-2012
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Issues and Topics, 1977-2009; 2; 3
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Chicago Tribune, 2000-2001; 2003; 2005; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Prosecution Politics, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Race - Death Penalty Articles (1 of 2), 1991; 1994-2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Race - Death Penalty Articles (2 of 2), 1992-1994; 1996-1997; 1999-2001; 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Race - General, 1997-2004; 2007; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Race - Official Studies and Law Reviews, 1986-1987; 1991; 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Race - Prisons, 1991-1994; 1998-1997; 2000; 2005; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Religion - Catholics, 1992; 1996-2000; 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Religion - Catholics, 2000-2007; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Religious Views - General, 2000-2004; 2007; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Religion - Jews, 1996-1997; 1999-2002; 2007-2009; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Resource Centers, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Statistics Through 2001, 1990-2001; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Statistics Through 2007, 2002-2007 (Box 5, Folder 8)